Now, you're going to get a chance to use SageMaker to build a model.
现在你将有机会使用 SageMaker 构建模型
To start with, open of
首先
sagemaker-deployment directory and then inside of that, the mini-projects directory.
打开 sagemaker-deployment 目录并找到 Mini-Projects 目录
The notebook we're going to be working in is,
我们将使用的 notebook 是
IMDB Sentiment Analysis-XGBoost( batch transform).
IMDB Sentiment Analysis-XGBoost (batch transform)
In this notebook, you're going to use SageMaker to create an XGBoost model,
在此 notebook 中 你将使用 SageMaker 创建一个 XGBoost 模型
that we'll try determine whether a review posted on
我们将使用该模型判断
the Internet movie database is positive or negative.
发布在 IMDB 数据库中的影评是正面的还是负面的
To begin with, step through the various cells that download the data,
首先看看各个单元格 包括下载数据
prepare the data, and process the data.
准备数据和处理数据
There isn't really anything for you to do here except execute the cells,
没有什么要执行的操作 只需执行这些单元格
and you should be warned that,
注意
the data processing can take some time,
数据处理流程可能要花费一段时间
for me it took almost a full hour.
我几乎花了整整一小时
So, I would recommend running all of the cells first,
建议先运行所有单元格
and then reading through to see what they're doing after the fact.
然后看看每一步的作用
Step four is where your work is going to begin.
第 4 步就需要你来操作了
To start, you will break the training data set up into a validation and training set,
首先 你需要将训练集拆分成验证集和训练集
then save the test training and validation sets to a file,
然后将测试集 训练集和验证集保存到文件中
and then upload those files to S3,
并将这些文件上传到 S3
just like we did in the Boston housing notebook.
就像在 Boston Housing notebook 中操作的那样
Then, you will create an XGBoost model, and fit it.
然后创建一个 XGBoost 模型 拟合该模型
Lastly, you will create a batch transform job to test the model,
最后创建一个批转换作业 测试模型
and take a look at how accurate your predictions are.
看看预测结果有多准确
Optionally, you can make sure to remove any files that were
最后一步 你可以选择删除
created in the data directory and the cache directory.
/data 目录和 /cache 目录下的所有文件
This just makes sure that the disk drive
这样的话
on your notebook instance doesn't get filled up too quickly.
notebook 实例不会很快就磁盘空间不足
I would recommend taking a look at the Boston housing notebook,
建议看看 Boston Housing notebook
as a lot of the things that we did there,
因为在此 notebook 中的很多操作
are going to translate into the tasks that you want to do in this notebook.
都与本 notebook 中的任务很相似
If you do get stuck however,
但是 如果你遇到问题的话
don't worry because in the next video,
别担心 在下个视频中
I'm going to go through in detail my solution.
我会详细讲解我的操作流程的